Hi, this is Liz Muller from Liz's Hair Design in Hollywood, Florida.
In this clip we're going to show you how to make a hair wrap.
Now, we're going to wrap this hair, I'm going to do it dry.
You're going to need a hair net, a brush, paddle brush, you're also going to need a bristle brush, because you want to smooth the hair out later on.
Taking it sections at a time, we're going to go around the hair, placing the hair in the middle, going around the head, nice and neatly, like this.
Make sure this is down here.
Now if you have a problem with that section here, and you have a lot of hair, it's giving you a problem, you could put a clip there so it doesn't get in the way, you can remove it afterwords, OK.
So just go around the hair, continue to go around and around.
It it was wet, you'd put like an actual thin piece of paper around it, it's really done easy too, but we're doing it dry.
Going to smooth it out like that, you might want to use a little product on it to just keep those little hairs down.
And you want to use a little product, a very small amount, maybe a little Slim del Lino, and just go like that to the hair.
And that's why you're going to pick up this brush next, because see all the little fine hairs, you're going to go ahead and brush those real straight, flat.
Nice and soft, really nice and easy, get every little hair there.
Placing it nice, and then we're going to use the hair wrap, and you're going to put it on the hair.
You're going to remove that pin in a minute, but you're going to wrap the hair like that.
This is Liz Muller, and this is how you make a hair wrap.